{
    "subject": "resource/Techno_Cumbia",
    "predicate": "property/name",
    "object": "Techno Cumbia",
    "human_readable": "The name of Techno Cumbia is Techno Cumbia.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9789188504219055,
            "question": "What is the name of Techno Cumbia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8244481086730957,
            "question": "What are some popular examples of Techno Cumbia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7802684307098389,
            "question": "Can you describe the characteristics of Techno Cumbia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7793451547622681,
            "question": "What instruments are commonly used in Techno Cumbia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7726853489875793,
            "question": "Are there any famous artists associated with Techno Cumbia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7710165977478027,
            "question": "Where did Techno Cumbia originate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7523614764213562,
            "question": "Is Techno Cumbia a genre of music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.748047947883606,
            "question": "What makes Techno Cumbia unique?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6301462650299072,
            "question": "How has Techno Cumbia evolved over time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5921280980110168,
            "question": "How has Techno Cumbia influenced other music genres?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of Techno Cumbia is Techno Cumbia.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1907_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How has Techno Cumbia evolved over time?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1907_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What makes Techno Cumbia unique?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1907_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Techno Cumbia a genre of music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1907_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1907_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1907_113.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1907_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1907_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1907_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1907_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1907_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1907_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1907_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1907_5.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the evaluation:\n\nThe triple statement is: \"Techno Cumbia\" is a Spanish-language uptempo techno-pop cumbia song.\n\nGiven the context information, here's my evaluation:\n\n* Document at file_path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1907/re-ranker-msmarco/16.txt mentions \"Techno Cumbia\" as a Spanish-language uptempo techno-pop cumbia song, which supports the triple.\n* Documents at file_path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1907/re-ranker-msmarco/45.txt (multiple instances) also support this statement by describing \"Techno Cumbia\" as a cumbia song that blends traditional cumbia with techno beats.\n* Document at file_path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1907/re-ranker-msmarco/5.txt mentions that the late Selena coined the term \u201ctechno cumbia,\u201d which further supports the triple.\n\nTherefore, the output is:\n\n{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents supports the statement that \"The name of Techno Cumbia is Techno Cumbia.\" This can be inferred from multiple references to the song titled \"Techno Cumbia\" in the given text."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}